export const data = [
    {
        question: "Which car is considered the Rolls Royce of JDMs?",
        option1: "Toyota Crown",
        option2: "Nissan President",
        option3: "Toyota Century",
        option4: "Nissan Laurel",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which JDM inspired the McLaren doors?",
        option1: "Mazda AZ-1",
        option2: "Toyota Sera",
        option3: "Nissan Silvia",
        option4: "Toyota MR2",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the engine code for the legendary engine found in the Toyota Supra MK4?",
        option1: "RB26DETT",
        option2: "13B-REW",
        option3: "EJ20",
        option4: "2JZ-GTE",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following JDM cars was originally available with a rotary engine?",
        option1: "Mazda RX-7",
        option2: "Subaru Impreza WRX STI",
        option3: "Nissan Silvia S15",
        option4: "Honda S2000",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following cars is known as the 'Godzilla' in the automotive world?",
        option1: "Mitsubishi Lancer Evolution X",
        option2: "Nissan GT-R R34",
        option3: "Toyota Supra MK4",
        option4: "Honda NSX",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which luxury line is an offspring of Toyota?",
        option1: "Lexus",
        option2: "Infiniti",
        option3: "Acura",
        option4: "Maybach",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What year did the first Toyota Crown Release?",
        option1: "1961",
        option2: "1947",
        option3: "1955",
        option4: "1972",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which Toyota model is known as the 'Godfather of Drift'?",
        option1: "Toyota Supra",
        option2: "Toyota Corolla AE86",
        option3: "Toyota MR2",
        option4: "Toyota Celica",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which Mitsubishi model was only made for the American Market and isn't considered a JDM?",
        option1: "Mitsubishi Lancer Evolution",
        option2: "Mitsubishi 3000GT",
        option3: "Mitsubishi FTO",
        option4: "Mitsubishi Eclipse",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What year was the Nissan Skyline GT-R first introduced?",
        option1: "1964",
        option2: "1969",
        option3: "1973",
        option4: "1980",
        ans: 2,
    },
]